RG 002:025, Behavioral Health Partnership Oversight Council
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut Behavioral Health Partnership Oversight Council records
2005-2009
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut Behavioral Health Partnership Oversight Council
2 cubic feet
The Council advises the Departments of Children and Families, and Mental Health and Addiction Services, and Social Services on the planning and implementation of the statutory Behavioral Health Partnership (BHP). Records are comprised of meeting summaries of the Council and its subcommittees.
RG002_025_BHPOC
Historical Note
The Behavioral Health Partnership Oversight Council was established in legislation (PA05-280 and later PA10-119) to advise the Departments of Children and Families (DCF), and Mental Health and Addiction Services (DMHAS), and Social Services (DSS) on the planning and implementation of the statutory Behavioral Health Partnership (BHP). Previously it was a subcommittee of the Medicaid Managed Care Council. The BHP Oversight Council is comprised of legislators and their designees, behavioral health consumers and advocates, medical and mental health practitioners, state agencies and insurers.
See also the website.
Scope and Content
Contains meeting summaries of the Council and its subcommittees. Meeting summaries include agendas, minutes, and supplemental material such as reports and presentations.
Arrangement
Arranged by year.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Community mental health services -- Connecticut -- Evaluation; Connecticut Behavioral Health Partnership Oversight Council -- Records and correspondence
Document Types:
Agendas (administrative records); Correspondence; Minutes (administrative records); Reports
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 2005-2009
  - 2005
    - Meeting summaries, 2005 September - December (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Membership, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Quality Management and Access Subcommittee meeting summaries, 2005 September - December (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Transition Subcommittee meeting summaries, 2005 September - November (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2006
    - Meeting summaries, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5-7)
    - Attendance, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Coordination of Care Subcommittee meeting summaries, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Operations Subcommittee meeting summaries, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Provider Advisory Subcommittee meeting summaries, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Quality Management and Access Subcommittee meeting summaries, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 12-14)
    - Trransition Subcommittee meeting summaries, 2006 January - March (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 2007
    - Meeting summaries, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 16-18)
    - Report: "Behavioral Health Partnership - Child Psychiatric Level of Care Guidelines", 2007 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Request for qualifications, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Coordination of Care Subcommittee meeting summaries, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 21-22)
    - Executive Committee, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Operations Subcommittee meeting summaries, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
    - Provider Advisory Subcommittee meeting summaries, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Quality Management and Access Subcommittee meeting summaries, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 5-7)
    - Transition Subcommittee meeting summaries, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 2008
    - Meeting summaries, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 9-11)
  - 2009
    - Meeting summaries, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 12)